[Music]
Hello, welcome to our channel Stock Market
Wizards. As Nifty was down by almost 2 today
and even after such a big correction,
this stock has
not given that big correction yet. This means
that the price of a stock is outperforming our major
index Nifty.
So in today's video, we
will analyze the price structure of III Lord General Insurance.
What type of price setup is this stock showing in its price,
due to which there can be an upward movement in the coming time
and
Ras Jad is also showing support for the price of this stock.
So, we will
cover the details now. Before that, if you have
not yet subscribed to the Stock Market channel, please
subscribe to the channel and if you
liked the video, then like the video. The
chart that has opened in front of your screen has
opened. The time frame selected for III Lord General Insurance is
weekly. If
you look at the stocks of the insurance sector,
all the stocks are currently
outperforming and the price of this stock is also currently outperforming
with the support of Rasio
chart, as always.  So the price follows a channel.
If the price goes up, it will
follow an uptrend channel. If it comes down, it will
follow a downtrend channel. If it
consolidates, it will consolidate within a flat channel.
Clearly, the
price of this stock is following an uptrend channel here.
As the price
moves towards the upper boundary of the channel, the price has
seen multiple times of supply here.
And as it moves towards the lower boundary,
look at the price, it has seen multiple times of
demand here. And finally,
in 2023, see the price tested the lower boundary of the channel here.
After that, the
price is continuously
creating a higher higher formation here. And this type of
setup is showing right now. Probably,
in the coming time, the price
can test the upper boundary of the channel. As soon as the
price tests the lower boundary of the channel, the
price is seeing demand here.
And exactly as it
tests the upper boundary, we will
see supply there, which is
becoming the level for now, approximately 2100.  Around 1265
because the price is following a good channel here ever since it was
listed. There
is a high probability that the type of weekly
time frame that is creating a higher high formation here
can test this upper boundary because see, the price was
following a downtrend channel here and has just
broken out of this downtrend channel. After breaking out,
see, it is continuously creating a higher high
formation here. And the type
of price setup that is showing right now, the price should
not break its previous swing low
which is being formed below
1265. The price should not break this level.
And as soon as the price breaks this high, a
further continuation
move can come here because see clearly, the
price is creating a higher high formation here.
As soon as it breaks this swing high, it will
create a swing high. And
here the price is creating a lower high formation
which is a positive sign in the price structure.
And in both the cases,
its previous swing low is being formed here.
Exit here.  The point can be decided
and this chart pattern will fail here
if it breaks this swing low,
otherwise in the coming time, there can be
continuation and upward movement here. Along with
that, support of Raso Chad is also
visible here, hence I open the
Raso chart of II GI Aaaa GI vs Nifty 500.
Nifty 500 Raso chart is
also trading around its multi-year support,
due to which there is a
sign here that this stock can outperform Nifty 500.
See, ever since it was listed in
mid-2017, whenever you look at the price, it is
coming around this low. The price is outperforming from here.
Exactly, right now it is
trading around the support of the same year,
which is the support of almost five years
and from the same level, right now a bounce
or outperformance is seen.
Look, the price already broke out of the
down trend channel from the top in 2021 on the Raso chart here,
its meaning was
that  The stock price
is about to outperform but still see the price
is sustaining around the support of the multitrend and
from here it is giving a sign of outperform because
of the Rashi chart, so the Rashi chart is
trading around the support of the multitrend here, a
higher high formation is being created here in the price structure due to which a
continuation move can come
and the price can go and test the upper boundary of the channel
which is becoming a level of
2100, the previous swing low which is being formed
around 1265,
you can place or modify the stop loss as per your risk, the
setup is strong,
if you get some deflection you can consider there and
as soon as the price breaks the swing high you will get
further confirmation here
and as per your wish manage the quantity from us,
I hope you are able to
understand the details, you liked the video, please
like the video and subscribe to the channel,
Namaskar Jai
[Sangeet]
Hind